YMCA
Young man there's no need to feel down
I said young man pick yourself off the ground
I said young man 'cos you're in a new town
There's no need to be unhappy
Young man there's a place you can go
I said young man when you're short on your dough
You can stay there and
I'm sure you will find many ways to have a good time
It's fun to stay at the
Y.M.C.A.
They have everything for young men to enjoy
You can hang out with all the boys
It's fun to stay at the
Y.M.C.A.
You can get yourself clean
You can have a good meal
You can do whatever you feel
Young man
Are you listenin' to me?
I said young man
What do you wanna be?
I said young man you can make clear your dreams
But you've got to know this one thing
No man does it all by himself
I said young man put your pride on the shelf
And just go there to the
Y.M.C.A. I'm sure they can help you today
It's fun to stay at the
Y.M.C.A.
They have everything for young men to enjoy
You can hang out with all the boys
It's fun to stay at the
Y.M.C.A.
You can get yourself clean
You can have a good meal
You can do whatever you feel
Young man
I was once in your shoes
I said
I was down and out with the blues
I felt no man cared if
I were alive
I felt the whole world was so jive
That's when someone came up to me
And said young man take a walk up the street
There's a place there called the
Y.M.C.A. They can start you back on your way
It's fun to stay at the
Y.M.C.A.
They have everything for young men to enjoy
You can hang out with all the boys
Y.M.C.A.
It's fun to stay at the
Young man, young man there's no need to feel down
Y.M.C.A.
Young man, young man pick yourself off the ground
It's fun to stay at the
Y.M.C.A.
Young man, young man
Are you listening to me?
What do you wanna be?
Young man, young man
You'll find it at the
Y.M.C.A.
No man, no man does it all by himself
Young man, young man put your pride on the shelf
And just go to the
Y.M.C.A.